Name: Ali Hassan

ID: F2020266448

Course Title: Advanced Web Technologies

Section: V1

Assignment# 1

Package.json

Index.html

AboutMe.jsx

Index.css:

```
# Secretary 2...

# Secretary Secretary Annual Secretary Secretary
```

```
# index.css > ...
.social-media a {
  font-size: 1.8em;
  text-decoration: none;
  transition: color 0.3s;
             .social-media a:hover {
    color: ■#1abc9c;
            .content h2 {
    color: ■73498db;
    borden-bottom: 2px solid ■#3498db;
    padding-bottom: 5px;
    margin-bottom: 28px;
    font-5ize: 1.8em;
    font-weight: 600;
AboutMe.jsx # index.css ×
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                    Ⅲ ...
           .content ul l1:before {
    content: "\2022";
    color: ##3498db;
    font-weight: bold;
    display: inline-block;
    width: lem;
    margin-left: -1em;
}
            .content a {
    color: ■#3498db;
    text-decoration: none;
    transition: color 0.3s;
           .content a:hover {
    color: ■#1abc9c;
            .skills-grid (
display: grid;
grid-template-columns: repeat(auto-fit, minmax(150px, ifr));
gap: 20px;
           .skill-card {
    background: ■#F0f2f5;
    border-radius: 18px;
    padding: 70px;
    text-align: center;
    transition: background 0.3s, transform 0.3s;
```

```
.skill-card:hover {
    background: ■#3498db;
    color: ■#fff;
    transform: translateY(-5px);
.skill-card:hover i {
color: ■#fff;
}
  .education-card,

.experience-card {

margin-bottom: 20px;

padding: 20px;

background: #efefofs;

border-radues: 10px;

box-shadow: 0 2px 10px □rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.1);
  utMe.jsx # index.css
   .experience-card h3 {
    margin: 0;
    font-size: 1.4em;
    color: #3498db;
    font-weight: 600;
     .education-card p,
.experience-card p {
  mangin: 5px 8;
  font-size: 1.1em;
  color: □#666;
    .education-card span,
.experience-card span {
   display: block;
   font-size: 0.9em;
   color: ■#999;
```

Content.jsx

```
## AboutMap | ## Octoor | ## O
```

Education.jsx

```
## Special Property | ## Special Property |
```

Experience.jsx

Header.jsx

Objectives.jsx

```
      ⊗ AboutMe.jsx

      ⊗ Objectives.jsx ×

    src > components > ⊗ Objectives.jsx > .
```

Portfolio.jsx

```
### AboutMisps | ### Armonanetes | ### Pentfolions | ### Armonanetes | ### Pentfolions | ### Armonanetes | ### Pentfolions | ### Pentfolio
```

Skills.jsx

Main.jsx

```
| Import Resct from 'react' | Import Resct from 'r/components/Meader' | Import AboutMe from 'r/components/Meader' | Import AboutMe from 'r/components/Meader' | Import AboutMe from 'r/components/Meader' | Import Skill from 'r/components/Skill' | Import Skyerlence from 'r/components/Experlence' | Import Skyerlence from 'r/components/Experlence' | Import Skyerlence from 'r/components/Experlence' | Import 'r/Indox.css | Im
```



About Me

Enthusiastic and skilled Front End Developer with over 3 years of experience building and maintaining responsive web applications. Proficient in JavaScript, React, HTML5, CSS3, and related front-end technologies. Strong problem-solving abilities with a keen eye for design and user experience.

Objectives

To utilize my expertise and experience as a Front End Developer to create visually appealing and user-friendly web interfaces, contributing to the success of projects and achieving client satisfaction.

Professional Skills







Sass



Bootstrap



Git & GitHub



Responsive Design

Education

Matricultation

Dar-e-Arqam School Institution

2016 - 2018

Intermediate

Punjab Group of Colleges

2019 - 2020

Bachelors in Computer Science

University of Management and Technology

2020 - 2024

Experience

Front End Developer

Hannan Tank Califfons

Experience

Front End Developer

Hassan Tech Solutions

2020 - Present

- Developed and maintained front-end components of web applications using JavaScript, React, HTML, and CSS.
- Collaborated with designers and back-end developers to ensure the seamless integration of UI/UX designs.
- Optimized web applications for performance, responsiveness, and cross-browser compatibility.

Junior Front End Developer

XYZ Innovations

2018 - 2020

- Assisted in the development of front-end features and user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Worked closely with senior developers to troubleshoot and resolve front-end issues.
- Participated in code reviews and contributed to the improvement of coding standards and best practices.

Portfolio

Portfolio

Here are a few projects that showcase my skills and experience:

- Project One A responsive e-commerce web application built with React and Bootstrap.
- Project Two A personal portfolio website created with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Project Three An interactive web application using React and Sass for styling.